{
    "subject": "resource/Smooth_Glasgow",
    "predicate": "ontology/shareSource",
    "object": "http://www.rajar.co.uk/listening/quarterly_listening.php",
    "human_readable": "The share source of Smooth Glasgow is http://www.rajar.co.uk/listening/quarterly_listening.php.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9640833735466003,
            "question": "What is the URL of the share source for Smooth Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9542030692100525,
            "question": "Where can you find the share source for Smooth Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9402655363082886,
            "question": "Which website hosts the share source information for Smooth Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9302069544792175,
            "question": "Can you describe the format of the share source for Smooth Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9296649694442749,
            "question": "What is the purpose of the share source for Smooth Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9291439652442932,
            "question": "Who maintains the share source for Smooth Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9089963436126709,
            "question": "Is the share source for Smooth Glasgow publicly accessible?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8957495093345642,
            "question": "What type of data does the share source for Smooth Glasgow provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8806408047676086,
            "question": "What kind of insights can be gained from the share source for Smooth Glasgow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8635053038597107,
            "question": "How often is the share source for Smooth Glasgow updated?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The share source of Smooth Glasgow is http://www.rajar.co.uk/listening/quarterly_listening.php.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4996_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of insights can be gained from the share source for Smooth Glasgow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4996_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of data does the share source for Smooth Glasgow provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4996_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the share source for Smooth Glasgow publicly accessible?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4996_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4996_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document for file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4996/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt` contains the information that \"share source = [http://www.rajar.co.uk/listening/quarterly_listening.php]\", which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}